identogo.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Identogo

## IDEMIA Online Privacy Statement

IDEMIA, IdentoGO® (a division of IDEMIA) and IDEMIA’s subsidiaries have created this Privacy Statement to provide information on how IDEMIA handles personal information and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This Privacy Statement applies to IDEMIA websites that link to this Privacy Statement. Additional information on our personal information practices may be provided in notices provided at the time of data collection. To the extent a notice provided at the time of collection conflicts with this Privacy Statement, such notice will control.

### The Collection of Personal Information

We may collect information, including personal information, about you as you use our websites and interact with us. "Personal information" is data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual, and may include name, address, email address, phone number, social media account information, or payment card number. You do not need to provide personal information simply to browse our website. If we link other data with your personal information, we will treat that linked data as personal information. We also collect personal information from trusted third-party sources and engage third parties to collect personal information to assist us (collectively “Business Partners”).

IDEMIA collects personal information to operate our business and for other legitimate purposes permitted by applicable law, such as to: 

  * Provide products or services you have purchased or requested, including fingerprint-based background checks. 
  * Provide customer service. 
  * Improve and personalize your experience on our website. 
  * Send marketing communications. 
  * Conduct surveys, marketing promotions, contests or giveaways. 
  * Manage an application for employment with IDEMIA.

In some instances, IDEMIA may automatically collect data through cookies, web logs, web beacons and other similar applications. This information is used to better understand and improve the usability, performance, and effectiveness of the website and to help tailor content or offers for you. Please read the ["Cookies and Other Web Technologies"](http://www.cisco.com/web/siteassets/legal/privacy_full.html#cookies) section below for more information.

### Your Choices

If you voluntarily provide personal information, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement. If, in connection with your use of a particular service, we ask to use your data in a way not described in this Privacy Statement and you do not wish to permit that use, you can choose not to use the particular service.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

IDEMIA keeps your personal information confidential. We will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Unless we have your permission, we will not use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to the ones described at the time you provide the data. IDEMIA engages service providers and suppliers ("Business Partners") to perform certain functions on MorphTrust's behalf. For example, Business Partners may provide services to you, maintain IDEMIA information technology systems, process credit card transactions, provide web hosting services and assist IDEMIA with marketing and communication initiatives. Business Partners will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to perform the services. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information received on MorphTrust’s behalf and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. Information provided by you to IDEMIA for the purpose of submitting to a background check will be shared with one or more government agencies as part of the background check process.

We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with applicable law, regulation or legal process served on Lexmark; (b) comply with requests for information from police or government authorities; (c) protect and defend the rights or property of IDEMIA (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (d) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of IDEMIA employees or members of the public.

IDEMIA or its affiliates could merge with or be acquired by another business or their respective assets may be acquired. IDEMIA will seek appropriate protection for personal information in these types of transactions.

### Security of Your Personal Information 

We protect the personal information entrusted to us and treat it securely in accordance with this Privacy Statement and applicable agreements with government agencies. IDEMIA implements physical, administrative, and technical safeguards to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also require that our suppliers protect such information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure. 

### Retention of Personal Information  

We will retain your personal information as needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. We will retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

### Use of Cookies and other Web Technologies 

Like many websites, IDEMIA uses automatic data collection tools, such as cookies, embedded web links and web beacons. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website, such as your browser type and the address of the website from which you arrived at our website. They may also collect information about:

  *  **Your Internet Protocol (IP) address**. This is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. It allows web servers to locate and identify your computer, this is a unique address assigned to your PC by your Internet service provider or information systems department on a TCP/IP network.
  *  **Clickstream Behavior.**  For example, the pages you view and the links you click.

These tools help make your visit to our website easier, more efficient and more valuable by providing you with a customized experience and recognizing you when you return. For more information about how we use automatic data collection tools, such as cookies and widgets, and your choices in relation to these tools, please see our [Cookie Policy](http://www.cisco.com/web/siteassets/legal/adct.html).

### Linked Websites 

We may provide links to other, third party websites and services that are outside of our control and not covered by this Privacy Statement. Third party websites that include links to a IDEMIA website are also outside of our control and not covered by this Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy statements posted on those websites (and all websites) you visit. 

### Children's Privacy 

IDEMIA does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18 and does not target its websites to children under the age of 18. If we learn that we have collected personal information from children under the age of 18, we will take steps to delete such information from our systems.

### Consent to Transfer, Processing and Storage of Personal Information 

IDEMIA may transfer your personal information to its business partners and contractors as described above. 

### Your California Privacy Rights 

Residents of the State of California, under California Civil Code § 1798.83, have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of your personal information by third parties (such as advertisers) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.
